[
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Nostoa communis",
    "Nostoc communae",
    "Nostoc comune",
    "Nostoc commune"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Nostoc commune"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Saccoriza polyschides",
    "Saccorhizaus polyschidee",
    "Saccorhiza polyschides",
    "Saccorhiza polyscoides"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Saccorhiza polyschides"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Fucus vesiculus",
    "Fucus vesiculae",
    "Fucuae vesiculosus",
    "Fucus vesiculosus"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Fucus vesiculosus"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Codium tomentosum",
    "Codiua tomentosue",
    "Codiua toemntosum",
    "Coddium tumentosum"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Codium tomentosum"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Ulvae lactucieae",
    "Ulva lactuca",
    "Ulva lactucae",
    "Ulva lactucae"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Ulva lactuca"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Chara vulgaris",
    "Chara vulgariae",
    "Charas vulgarie",
    "Charae vulgarium"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Chara vulgaris"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Fomea fomentaria",
    "Fomeae fomentarius",
    "Fomes fommentarius",
    "Fomes fomentarius"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Fomes fomentarius"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Lycoperdon perlatum",
    "Lycoperdum perlatum",
    "Lycoperdum perlagum",
    "Lycoperdon perlagum"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Lycoperdon perlatum"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Astraeus higrometrycus",
    "Astraeus hygrometricus",
    "Astraeus hygrometrycus",
    "Astreus higrometrycus"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Astraeus hygrometricus"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Crucibulum laeve",
    "Crucibulua laeva",
    "Crucibulua laevus",
    "Crucibulun laeve"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Crucibulum laeve"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Lactarius deliciosus",
    "Lactaria deliciosae",
    "Lactarius deliciosa",
    "Lactariae deliciosus"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Lactarius deliciosus"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Boletus edibilis",
    "Boletus edulis",
    "Boletus edibulum",
    "Boletus edulias"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Boletus edulis"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Amanita muscaria",
    "Amanita muscharia",
    "Amanita musscaria",
    "Amanita muschiria"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Amanita muscaria"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Everniae prunastris",
    "Evernia prunastri",
    "Evernia prunastris",
    "Everniaus prunastre"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Evernia prunastri"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Pseudoevernia furfuracea",
    "Pseudeverniaus furfuracee",
    "Pseudevernia furfuracea",
    "Pseudoevernia furfuracea"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Pseudevernia furfuracea"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Ramalinae farhinacea",
    "Ramalinae farinacea",
    "Ramalina farinaceas",
    "Ramalina farinacea"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Ramalina farinacea"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Usneaus barvata",
    "Usneaus barbata",
    "Usnea barbataea",
    "Usnea barbata"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Usnea barbata"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Lasalia pustulata",
    "Lasallia pustulata",
    "Lasallia pustulatea",
    "Lasalia pustulatea"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Lasallia pustulata"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Lobarieae pulmonarias",
    "Lobaria pulmonaria",
    "Lobarie pulmonarium",
    "Lobaria pulmonarias"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Lobaria pulmonaria"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Xanthobia parietina",
    "Xantoriae pariatina",
    "Xantoria parietina",
    "Xanthoria parietina"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Xanthoria parietina"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Rhizocarpon geographicum",
    "Rhizocarpon geographicus",
    "Rhizocarpoa geographicue",
    "Rhizocarpoa geographicum"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Rhizocarpon geographicum"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Parmelia quecinus",
    "Parmelia quercinea",
    "Parmelia quercina",
    "Parmelia querchina"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Parmelia quercina"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Peltigea membranacea",
    "Peltigea membranacaea",
    "Peltigera membranea",
    "Peltigera membranacea"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Peltigera membranacea"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Polytrichus formosus",
    "Polytriccum formosum",
    "Polytriccus formosus",
    "Polytrichum formosum"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Polytrichum formosum"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Grimmia pulvinatae",
    "Grimia pulvinata",
    "Grimmiaus pulvinate",
    "Grimmia pulvinata"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Grimmia pulvinata"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Hypnum cupresiforme",
    "Hypnum cupressiforme",
    "Hypnua cupressiformeis",
    "Hypnus cupresiforme"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Hypnum cupressiforme"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Homalothecium sericeae",
    "Homalothecium sericeum",
    "Homalotecium sericea",
    "Homalothecius sericeum"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Homalothecium sericeum"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Lunularia crusciata",
    "Lunnularia cruciatea",
    "Lunularia cruciata",
    "Lunulariae cruciata"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Lunularia cruciata"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Marchantya polimorpha",
    "Marchantea polimorpha",
    "Marchantia polymorpha",
    "Marchantia polymorphea"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Marchantia polymorpha"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Frullania dilatatta",
    "Frusllania dilastata",
    "Frullania dilatata",
    "Frutas Tania DILO TATA!!"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Frullania dilatata"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Teridium achilinum",
    "Pteridium achillinum",
    "Pteridium achilinum",
    "Pteridium aquilinum"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Pteridium aquilinum"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Dryopteris afina",
    "Dryhpteris affiniae",
    "Dryopteris affinis",
    "Dryopteria affinia"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Dryopteris affinis"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Polystichum setiferum",
    "Polysticum setiferum",
    "Polystichum setifurum",
    "Polysticum settiferum"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Polystichum setiferum"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Aspleniaum tricomanes",
    "Asplenium trichomanes",
    "Asplenium tricomanes",
    "Asplenius trichomanes"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Asplenium trichomanes"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Aspleniua ceterace",
    "Asplenium ceterachea",
    "Asplenium ceterach",
    "Asplenium cheterach"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Asplenium ceterach"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Polypodhium vulgaria",
    "Polipodium vulgaris",
    "Polypodium vulgare",
    "Polypodium vulgaris"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Polypodium vulgare"
},
{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre correcto de esta especie?",
  "options": [
    "Struthioptheris spicant",
    "Struthioptheria spinacant",
    "Struthiopteris spicant",
    "Strutiopteris spinaca"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Struthiopteris spicant"
}
]
